爸爸去猎魔了
Dad's on a hunting trip
好几天没回家了
and he hasn't been home in a few days.
(忆往昔)
我们应付得来几个小女巫
We could take care of a few kitchen witches.
他们的法力来自恶魔
They get their power from demons.
在十字路口卖灵魂那种
I mean, selling your soul at the crossroads kind of deal?
你们是女巫养大的  却成了猎人
So you guys were raised by a witch, but you're hunters.
对
Yep.
海斯博士想了解一切
Dr. Hess wants to know everything
我们的"朋友"温家兄弟的事
about our "Friends" The Winchesters --
他们的同盟
their allies...
他们的习惯
...their habits.
萨姆的头发怎么会那么油亮
how does Sam get his hair so shiny?
当我看到大衮抓走了凯莉
When I saw Dagon had captured Kelly,
我觉得天使能帮上忙
I thought the angels could help.
怎么样呢
And?
该把这个毁掉了
Time to take this off the board.
不
No!
我现在知道  这个孩子必须降生
I know now that this child must be born
并且保留他的法力
with all of his power.
(如今)
(怀俄明州  罗克河)
(山眠寄宿  日租&长期)
有人吗
Hello?
你得按铃
You have to ring the bell.
你吓我一跳
You startled me.
你可真娇气
What a delicate constitution you must have.
戒指真好看
Uh, that is a lovely ring.
是啊
Yes.
如果它丢了
And if it goes missing,
我就知道该找谁了
I'll know who to blame.
如果需要  我可以清理你的气
I could cleanse your aura if you like.
似乎有点浑浊
Looks a little...muddy.
来了
Coming!
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉让您久等
Sorry for the wait.
-你是塔莎吗  -塔莎·贝恩斯  是的
- Are you Tasha? - ‭Tasha Banes, yes.
-我打过电话  -是的  我是安迪
- I called and... - Yes, right. I'm Andy.
我们为您安排了楼上的房间
We've got you set up at the top of the stairs.
太好了
Fantastic.
您为什么会来罗克河
So what brings you to Rock River?
公事还是私事
Business or pleasure?
都有吧
Little bit of both.
(艾莉西娅  没事吧)
现形
Reveal.
马上
Now.
现形
Reveal.
马上
Now.
现形
Reveal.
天呐
Oh, God.
[邪恶力量 第12季第20集]
好吧  昨晚
Okay, so last night...
超级马里奥开外挂的那一幕
that Super Mario power-up crap?
那不是小卡
That wasn't Cass.
那个宝宝还没出生呢
That freaking baby isn't even born yet
就已经控制了他
and it sock puppeted him.
想想看
Think about it.
小卡说他对小路西法有信心
Cass said that he had faith in Lucifer Jr.?
那是什么意思
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
我不知道
I don't know.
听着  我也搞不懂  迪恩
I mean, look, this doesn't make any sense to me either, Dean.
但如果我们还想找到小卡
But if we wanna have some shot at finding Cass,
那我们就得
then we have to...
我不知道  尽量去从他的角度想
I don't know. Uh, try and think like him.
怎么想
How?
说真的  在此之前  如果小卡搞砸了
Seriously, I mean up until now, if Cass messed up,
如果他做错了事
if he did something wrong,
但他以为是出于正义的理由  我都理解
but he thought it was for the right reasons, I got it.
是吧
Right?
但昨晚  我看着他时
But last night, when I looked at him,
我不认得与我对视的那个人
I did not recognize the guy staring back at me.
你能修好吗
Can you fix it?
希望能
I hope so.
-不是我的  -也不是我的
- It's not me. - ‭It's not me.
肯定是妈妈的
Must be one of Mom's.
喂
Hello? ‭
萨姆
Sam?
我不知道...我是艾莉西娅·贝恩斯
Uh, I didn't know y-- Uh, it's Alicia Banes.
艾莉西娅  怎么回事
Alicia? Hey, what's going on?
-麦克斯和艾莉西娅吗  -嗯
- Like Max and Alicia? - ‭Yeah.
抱歉  玛丽给了我
Yeah, sorry to, um... Uh, Mary gave me
好几个可以联络她的号码  我们觉得...
a couple different numbers to reach her, and we thought --
不  不
No. No.
我觉得玛丽可能会愿意帮忙
I thought Mary would be down to help.
给我们打个援手
Uh, be our backup on this, um...
你在说疯话
You sound crazy.
两位  我是迪恩
Hey, guys. It's Dean.
-你们没事吧  -嗯  看你问谁了
- Uh, you okay? - Yeah, depends who you ask.
妈妈去追捕一个
Um, Mom was hunting this witch
在怀俄明州到处杀人的女巫
who's killed people all over Wyoming.
总之  妈妈一般
Uh, anyway, Mom usually
会跟我们报平安  但她失联了
checks in with us, but she's sort of disappeared.
天呐  她才没失联
Oh, my God. She did not disappear.
不过是在忙
She's busy.
等等  那么你们的妈妈的确不见了吗
Wait, so -- so your mom is missing?
你们在哪
Where are you guys?
我们正要往怀俄明州罗克河去
We're on our way to Rock River, Wyoming.
但麦克斯觉得我在小题大做
But Max thinks I'm overreacting, but I --
因为你就是太夸张了
Because you're being dramatic.
妈妈没事的  别打扰他们了
Mom's fine. Stop bothering them.
好啊  好吧
Fine. Okay.
我们不会有事的  没事了
Hey, we'll be okay. Uh, never mind.
不  等等
No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
把地址发给我们  我们去跟你们碰头吧
Hey, why don't you text us your address? We'll meet you.
是吗
You will?
-是什么  -我们回头见
- They will what? - We'll see you soon.
搞什么  小卡怎么办
What the hell, man? What about Cass?
哥们  小卡丢了手机
Dude, Cass ditched his cellphone.
乔迪给小卡和凯莉发了三州
Look, Jody put an APB out for Cass and Kelly
全境通告
across three states.
直到收到什么回报
Until that shakes something loose
或是找到了别的线索
or we get some other break,
我们就只能干坐着
all we're doing is -- is sitting here,
拿头撞墙
banging our heads against a brick wall.
我们出去...
Let's get out there. Let's...
他们的妈妈去猎魔  一周没回家了
Their mom's on a hunting trip and hasn't been home in a week.
好吧  走
All right. Let's go.
(拨打妈妈的手机)
行行好  把那玩意关掉
Please be a dear and shut that bloody thing off.
-是迪恩  -怎么了
- It's Dean. - And?
我是玛丽  请留言
This is Mary. Leave a message.
妈妈
Mom.
我就想告诉你
Hey, uh, just wanted to let you know that, uh,
我和萨姆  我们要去办个案子
me and Sam, we're uh, we're heading out on a case
跟那对儿巫师双胞胎  麦克斯和艾莉西娅
with those witch twins, uh, Max and Alicia.
我回头把信息发给你
Um, I'll text you the info, but, uh...
我知道英国人让你忙得脚不着地
I know the Brits have got you running nonstop.
如果你能帮忙  那太好了
So if you can help out, that'd be great.
就算你不能过来
And even if you can't swing by,
能回个电话吗
can you call me back?
就是发生了些事
Just some stuff going down that's...
让我有点承受不来
kind of got me spun out.
能跟你聊聊就好了
Be good to talk to you.
你一定觉得变成玛丽很好玩
I suppose it amuses you to take Mary's form,
或许你是觉得这会
or perhaps you believe it will inspire
让我不愿下手
a bit of hesitation on my part.
不会的
It will not.
他不会开口的
He's not gonna talk.
这个易形者杀了人  玛丽
The shifter has killed people, Mary.
它活该受折磨  这还只是个开头
This is the very beginning of what it deserves.
如果它肯说出它的家人在哪
And if it tells us where its family is,
这一切都会停止
well, then this will all stop.
我保证
Promise.
你撒谎的时候  眼睛会抽动
That eye of yours twitches when you lie.
我的眼睛老抽动
My eye twitches all the time.
那么
Well, then,
看来我完全了解你了
I guess I know all about you.
你们好
Hey, guys.
好吧  我们到了  什么情况
All right, well, we're here. What do you got?
我们的妈妈去抓一个"借力者"巫师了
Our mom was after a "borrower" witch.
就是通过恶魔交易得到法力的巫师
So witch that gets their power from a demon deal.
好吧  那么你们追踪你们妈妈来到了这儿
Okay, so you tracked your mom here?
现在我们又追踪她
And now we tracked her
到了镇上一家素食餐厅
to the only vegan restaurant in town.
他们告诉了我们她住在了哪
They told us where she was staying.
还有吗
Anything else?
我拿到了酒保的号码
I got the bartender's phone number.
别理他
Ignore him.
迪恩
Dean...
那车还是那么美
that car is still major.
想看看吗
You want the tour?
-当然了  -来吧
- Definitely. - ‭Come on.
嗯
Yeah.
麦克斯觉得根本没事
Max isn't really feelin' this.
嗯  没发现呢
Yeah, I hadn't noticed. ‭
他总觉得他更了解妈妈
He always thinks he knows Mom better,
但是  那是因为他们都是天生巫师
but it's 'cause they're both natural witches.
他们就那样
It's who they are.
是吧
Right?
-不错嘛  -嗯
- Nice. - ‭Yeah.
-那是榴弹发射器吗  -是的
- Is that a grenade launcher? - Yes, she is.
嗯  但这才是我们现在需要的
Yeah, but, uh, this is what we need right now.
杀女巫的子弹
Witch killing bullets.
你呢  魔法方面
And what about you? Uh, with magic.
没有  我没有
Nah, I don't have it.
对我来说就像白噪
It's just kind of a lot of noise to me.
魔法是他们的专长
Magic is definitely their thing, you know?
嗯
Yeah.
小时候  迪恩和我爸爸
When I was growing up, Dean and my dad
一起猎魔  那是他们的纽带
had the same thing with hunting, that bond.
和玛丽呢
What about with Mary?
她...
I mean, she, uh,
她去查案  就失踪了
she gets into a case and just sort of vanishes.
嗯  玛丽是个好猎人
Yeah. No, Mary's a great hunter.
是啊
Yeah.
她似乎不怎么喜欢拥抱
Uh, she doesn't seem like much of a hugger.
是啊
Yeah.
我们去找你们妈妈吧
Let's go find your mom.
她的车在
Well, her car's here.
没人打算把它藏起来  这是好事
Well, no one's trying to hide it. That's good news.
嗯
Yeah.
一点也不奇怪呢
Not weird. At all.
好吧  如果有情况  你们待在我们身后
All right, look, anything happens, you guys stay behind us.
嗯  好
Yeah. Sure.
艾莉西娅
Alicia...
有什么需要吗
Can I help you?
是的  我们在找...
Yes, please. We're, uh, we're looking for, uh --
麦克斯  艾莉西娅
Max? Alicia?
你们俩怎么来了
What are you two doing here?
妈妈
Mom!
萨姆和迪恩·温彻斯特
Sam and Dean Winchester,
这位是伟大的塔莎·贝恩斯
meet the great Tasha Banes.
孩子们跟我说了你们不少好话
The kids have told me very nice things.
艾莉西娅差不多逼他们来的  担心你有事
Alicia basically made them come just in case you were in peril.
根本没这必要
Well, that was unnecessary,
不过还是感谢你们了
but very nice of you all the same.
安迪  能给我的孩子
Andy, can we get a couple rooms
和他们的朋友安排房间吗
for my children and their friends?
当然  这就好
Sure. It'll just be a minute.
太好了  你们去我屋等吧
Great. You can wait in my room.
我有酒
I have wine. ‭
太好了
Great.
酒
Wine.
罗克河是死路一条  很遗憾  这里没有巫师
So Rock River's a dead end. No witches here, unfortunately.
我以为真是这里呢
Thought this was the place --
那你怎么不打电话
Well, then why didn't you call us?
我们
I mean, we...
我打了好几通电话  发了好多短信
I called and texted a lot.
对不起  我的手机一天没充电了
I'm sorry, baby. My phone hasn't been charging all day.
但我找到了个很棒的针灸医生
Oh, but I did find a fantastic acupuncturist.
-当然了  -当然了
- Of course you did. - Of course you did.
要我帮忙吗
You want me to help with that?
-我行的  -但你一向会在
- Oh, I've got it. - No, but you always call
猎魔第四天打电话的  从无例外
on the fourth day of a hunt, no matter what.
真的  我就是忘...
Honestly, babe, it just slipped my --
妈妈  你没事吧
Mom? You okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
萨姆  请吧
Sam, do the honors.
-好  -艾莉西娅  放点音乐
- Of course. - ‭Alicia, put some music on.
我从那家素食餐厅点了吃的
I ordered food from that vegan place,
但不送餐
but no deliveries.
-我去拿吧  -我去吧
- Oh, I can get it. - Oh, I'll grab it.
你们留下  聊聊天什么的
Uh, you guys stay, hang out, catch up.
迪恩  喝吧
Dean...drink.
好啊
Yes.
(待机)
我得说  我现在非常兴奋
I must say, I am pumping with adrenaline.
或许我们可以找个僻静的地方  活动一下
Perhaps we could find some privacy and tire ourselves out.
虽然不像在旅馆那样偷偷摸摸
It's not illicit motel sex, but --
我记得我们说好那是仅此一次
I remember us agreeing that was a onetime thing.
是吗  好吧
Did we? Ah, well.
凯奇  你的折磨就是浪费时间
Ketch, it was a waste of time, that little torture session.
你是指信息收集吗
Oh, you mean the information gathering session?
是啊  但我们没得到任何情报
Yeah, but we didn't get any intel.
那个易形者根本不会背叛家族
That shifter was never gonna betray his family,
但你还是
and still you --
有时候痛苦好使  有时候不好使
Sometimes pain works. Sometimes it doesn't.
但告诉你折磨不是办法的人
But anyone who tells you that torture is never the answer,
是自己没挨过刀
they haven't been under the knife.
但你很享受  因为刚刚
But you enjoyed it, because that...
我从未见过你的那一面
I have never seen that side of you.
是啊  玛丽  很遗憾  你不会成为
Yes, well, Mary, I'm sad to say that you won't become
英国记录者的蟋蟀杰米尼的
the Jiminy Cricket of the British Men of Letters.
我们不需要一个良心
We don't need a conscious.
说来老套  但我们坚定认为
Such a trite idea, but we firmly believe
为了结果可以不择手段
the ends do justify the means.
这次就不行
They didn't this time.
但是  你这不还没走吗
Ah, but look, you're still with us.
你大可以打给米克·戴维斯
Feel free to call Mick Davies.
让他给我记过
Have him write me up.
米克不接电话
Well, Mick's not answering his phone.
也不再发邮件了
And his e-mails have stopped.
他肯定忙着呢
I'm sure he's busy.
被长老叫去伦敦
When you get called to London by the old men,
可不是去喝酒逛街的
it's not all pints of stout and trips to Savile Row.
你大概该回迪恩的电话
Oh, and you should probably return Dean's call.
可别让他觉得妈妈不爱他
Wouldn't want him to think Mummy doesn't love him.
(没有新留言)
在等电话吗
Expecting a call? ‭
艾莉西娅
Alicia...
-看来不会了  -待会儿
- Guess not. - ...let's say later, I...
我可能需要开你的吉普
hypothetically might need your Jeep
-出去兜兜风  -还是算了
- to take it out for maybe a little cruise. - Mm, let's not.
我得说  你把他俩养得很不错
You know, I gotta say, you did a bang up job with those two. ‭
你肯定是喝醉了
You must be drunk.
喝红酒喝醉吗
Off of wine?
-不公平  -嗯
- Not fair. - Yeah.
我为麦克斯和艾莉西娅尽力了
I did the best I could for Max and Alicia.
-不  -我是走运
- No. - ‭I got lucky.
我看到你跟他们在一起的样子了  这很好
I see how you are with them, all right? It's good.
他们很开心
You know, they're -- they're happy.
艾莉西娅说你是猎着魔长大的
Alicia said you grew up in the life.
是啊  我爸爸从小教我和萨姆猎魔
Yeah. Yeah, my dad raised me and Sam to hunt.
你妈妈呢
And your mother?
一言难尽
That's complicated.
嗯  好吧
Yeah. Yeah.
家庭一向如此
Family's always complicated.
父母看上去总是似乎明智  强大  完美
Parents always seem smart and strong and perfect.
但你长大后才意识到
It's only when you grow up that you realize
他们也是人
that they're just people.
就算你不能过来
And even if you can't swing by,
能回个电话吗
can you call me back?
就是发生了些事
Just some stuff going down that's...
让我有点承受不来
kind of got me spun out.
能跟你聊聊就好了
Be good to talk to you.
我又不能用经济舱飞他过去
Well, I can't just send him to you economy comfort,
是吧
now can I?
包裹已经在军械库了
The package is in the armory now.
我们登记了号码
We gave it a lot number.
1-2-2-5-7.
你到了我们再聊
We'll speak when you get in.
再见
Tra.
(迪恩  进入语音信箱)
你挺自在啊
You've made yourself at home.
有事吗
Can I help you with something?
我用米克的电脑查邮件
I use Mick's computer for e-mail.
好啊  请吧
Uh, uh, yeah, well, have at it.
(米克  多留几日)
米克发来了新消息
There's a message from Mick.
他说他要在伦敦多留几周了
He says he's gonna be stuck in London a few more weeks.
这不就得了
Well...there you are.
食物
Food!
-谁饿了  -我
- Who's hungry? - ‭Me!
-天呐  谢谢  -太好了
- Oh, my goodness. Thank you. - All right.
-好香啊  -看看都有什么
- Ooh, it smells so good. - All right, let's see what we've got.
-我来摆桌子吧  -好嘞
- Here, I can set up over here. - Okay.
-我们就回来  -嗯
- We'll be right back, y'all. - Sure.
你俩摆好桌子  拿点餐巾纸
Ah, you two. Get it -- get it down. Grab some napkins.
我见过那表情  怎么了
I know that look. What's up?
这是贴在餐厅外面的
This was posted outside the restaurant.
(失踪  里克·沃什)
之前我们见到从地窖出来的人
That guy we saw earlier, coming out of the cellar?
他已经失踪一个月了
He's been missing for a month.
好吧  挺奇怪
Okay, that's weird.
或许塔莎错了
Well, maybe Tasha's wrong.
或许这里的确有问题
Maybe there is something going on here.
-嗯  我去告诉他们  -不不
- Yeah. I'll let 'em know. - No, no, no. Let's...
我们能解决的  走吧
We can handle it. Come on.
这是迪恩的另一部另一部电话
This is Dean's other other cell,
你知道该怎么做
so you must know what to do.
是我
It's me.
抱歉我之前没接  我跟凯奇猎魔去了
Sorry I couldn't pick up before. I've been on a hunt with Ketch.
迪恩
And, Dean...
很抱歉我一直没有陪伴你和萨姆
I'm sorry I haven't been there for you and Sam.
但我想陪你们
But I wanna be.
我会的
I will be.
我只是
I just...
需要完成这个
I need to finish this.
我想你们
I miss you boys.
我爱你们
I love you.
她逼我下了车
...she made me get out of the car... ‭
-才没有  -让我在雨里接电话
- She did not. - ...to make a phone call in the rain.
-天呐  艾莉西娅  -他就是下车来吼我
- Oh, my God. Alicia. - He just got out to yell at me.
一股腐臭味儿
‭Smells like death.
嗯
Yeah. ‭
你去吧
Go ahead.
什么  你去
What? You.
好吧
All right.
-艾莉西娅  -有那么严重吗
- Alicia... - Was it that serious?
天呐
Oh, man.
女士们  我要留下你们两个女的
Ladies, I'm gonna leave you alone now
谈谈心了
to have some girl time.
你什么时候不参与女人谈心了
Since when are you not a part of girl time?
我跟那个素食餐厅的
Since I've got a date with that hot bartender
性感酒保有约
from that vegan restaurant.
我们要享受点  男人时光
We're gonna have some... guy time.
可别做什么我不会做的事
Hey, don't do anything I wouldn't do.
嗯  好啊
Right. Right.
那能是什么呢
And what exactly was that?
麦克斯
Max!
萨姆
Sam.
迪恩
Dean.
该死
Son of a bitch.
-她的心被掏了  -他们的也是
- Her heart's been ripped out. - So have theirs.
等等  这是那栋房子里的每个人了
Wait, this is everybody that's in the house.
好吧  如果这是真塔莎
Okay, well, if this is the real Tasha,
那刚刚楼上跟我说话的是谁
then who the hell was I talking to up there?
麦克斯
Hey, Max. Uh...
我看到光了  你们找到什么麻烦了吗
I saw the light. You guys find some trouble to get into?
不不  我们...
Nah. No, no. We -- we -- we just, uh...
我刚刚还...
I just...
米克
Mick.
(拒绝进入)
拜托  快开啊
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
(拒绝进入)
(盖思·菲茨杰拉德)
(克莱尔·诺瓦克)
(艾琳·莱希)
搞什么
What the...
(迪恩·温彻斯特)
(地堡)
我们要向低配版的克里斯蒂安·贝尔汇报了
So now we're reporting to low-rent Christian Bale?
不是吧
Seriously?
我不喜欢那家伙  他让我不舒服
I don't like that guy. He creeps me out.
这是迪恩的另一部另一部电话
This is Dean's other other cell,
你知道该怎么做
so you must know what to do.
迪恩  打给我
Dean, call me.
我们有麻烦了
We've got a problem.
你好  玛丽
Hello, Mary.
你的掌纹是无法打开这个房间的
Your handprint doesn't open this room
因为你就不该进来
because it's not for you.
你在做什么
What are you doing here?
为什么米克的尸体在一个盒子里
Why is Mick's body in a box?
是很不幸的狼人事故
An unfortunate werewolf mishap.
狼人
A werewolf
一枪爆了他的头吗
shot him in the head?
并非不可能
It's not impossible.
你是个变态
You're a psychopath.
玛丽
Mary.
你杀了他吗
Did you kill him?
米克太软弱  他不像我们
Mick was weak. He wasn't one of us.
你什么时候才能明白  我们会不惜一切
When will you realize that we will do whatever it takes
铲除这世间的怪物
to rid this world of the things that go bump in the night?
这是米克和你的儿子们
Something that people like Mick and your sons
做不到的
are incapable of.
别提我的儿子
Don't talk about my boys.
为什么
Why not?
我收拾他们的烂摊子有好几个月了
I've been cleaning up after them for months.
我解决了那些他们
I took care of those federal agents
不该留活口的联邦探员
they stupidly allowed to live.
我杀了一个被他们视为人类的灵力少女
I killed a psychic girl they thought was...human.
老实说  他们太大意了
Honestly, they're damn sloppy.
我觉得你是想说
I think you mean...
正派
decent.
美国猎人完了
It's the end for the American Hunters.
他们的时代结束了
Their time has passed.
但我可以保护你
But I can keep you safe.
只要你肯听话
If you just play your part,
只要你乖乖配合
if you play nice...
我从不会乖乖的
I don't play nice.
打够了没
Are we done?
那天使铁莲花
Those Enochian brass knuckles
只对天使有用  很遗憾  我不是天...
only work on angels. And sadly, I'm not an --
铁莲花就是铁莲花
Brass knuckles are brass knuckles.
你个贱人
Oh, you bitch!
-不  我觉得他真...  -你是谁
- No, I think he's really - Who are you?
麦克斯
Max?
你把我妈妈怎么了
What did you do to my mom?
-麦克斯  你干什么  -等等
- Max! What are you - Wait, wait, wait.
告诉我
Tell me!
-你干什么  -放开她
- What are you doing? - Let her go!
-那不是你妈妈  -什么
- That's not your mom. - What?
你说什么呢  妈妈
What are you talking -- Mom!
等等  没事的
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. It's okay.
麦克斯  怎么了  亲爱的
Max, what is wrong, sweetie?
别  你不是我妈妈
Don't! Don't. You are not my mom.
-麦克斯  -我不知道你是什么
- Max - ‭I don't know what kind of thing you are,
但你不是我妈妈
but you are not my mom.
麦克斯  住手
Max! Stop!
现形  马上
Reveal. Now! ‭
现形
Reveal!
走廊尽头的房间
The...the room, end of the hall.
最顶楼
Top of the stairs.
魔法
Magic.
走
‭Got him.
麦克斯
Max!
妈妈
Mom!
不是吧
Really?
还有人想睡觉呢
People are trying to sleep.
好了  女士  玩乐时间结束了
All right, lady, craft time's over.
妈妈  妈妈
Mom! Mom!
萨姆  这魔法是怎么回事
Sam, this magic, what is this?
我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
我多幸运啊
How lucky am I?
这么厉害的巫师
Such an impressive witch.
或许你会接受上一个贱人不肯接受的协议
Maybe you'll take the deal the last bitch wouldn't.
我妈妈  你杀了她
My mother...you killed her.
是吗
Did I?
你把那些人怎么了
What did you do to those people?
我来给你们看
Let me show you.
我漫长的生命就要终结了
I'm reaching the end of my very long life,
这是个问题  因为我为法力出卖了灵魂
and it's a problem 'cause I sold my soul for power.
等我去世  我的灵魂会下地狱
So when I pass, my soul goes to Hell.
除非  我能找人承担我的重担
Unless I can find someone to take the burden,
接受我的魔法
to take my magic.
萨姆  妈妈
Sam! Mom!
你妈妈找到我后
When your mother found me,
当我意识到她是什么时
and when I realized what she was,
我提议教她
I offered to teach her.
我提议给她我的法力
I offered her my power.
但就算她要死了  也很粗鲁
But even dying, she was rude.
所以
So...
我把她做成了我的玩偶
I made her into one of my creatures.
那个玩偶有你妈妈全部的记忆
That doll has all of your mother's memories.
那差不多就是她
It's her. Mostly.
就像其他人
Just like the others.
里克  安迪  他们完全听从我的
Rick, Andy -- they do what I want, when I want.
我老了  我有自己的习惯
I'm old. I like things a certain way.
不
No.
No!
想得美
Nice try.
如果你杀了我
If you kill me,
那他们都会分崩离析
well, then all of them just fall apart.
我的提议是
So here's the offer.
你接受我的法力
You take my power.
承担我的重担  继承我的玩偶  你妈妈
You take my burden, and my doll -- your mother --
就能永远陪伴你和你妹妹
will stay with you and your sister forever.
一个快乐的大家庭
Just one big happy family.
麦克斯  不  听我说
Max, no. Listen to me.
你妈妈已经死了
Your mother is gone, okay?
虽然很糟糕  但是...
It's awful and it sucks... ...but that's
那么
So...
成交吗
do we have a deal?
你没事吧
You okay?
妈妈
Mom!
不
No! ‭
接受
Take it...
交易就完成
and the deal is done.
接受吧
Take it.
艾莉西娅
Alicia.
撑住  放松  放松
Hey, hold on. Just -- just take it easy. Take it easy.
我们会找人救你的
We're gonna get you some help.
-你为什么  -麦克斯  听我说
- Why did you... - Max, listen to me.
我必须那么做
I had to, okay?
那交易不是跟她做  是跟一个恶魔
That deal wasn't with her. It was with a demon.
你碰那魔法  你就会失去灵魂
You even touch that magic, you lose your soul.
迪恩
Dean!
快走
Come on.
别用劲  放松点
Don't fight. Don't -- Shh, shh. Just take it easy, okay?
呼吸
Take a breath.
艾莉西娅
Alicia?
她...
She, uh...
艾莉西娅
Alicia?
什么
What?
不要啊
Please. No, no, no.
Please, no. No, no, no!
麦克斯  这...
Hey, Max, um, this is, uh...
你现在可能还很震惊
Look, you -- you're probably in shock right now,
但那会过去的
but it's gonna pass.
然后会很痛苦
And then it's gonna hurt.
我本可以救她们的
I could've saved them...
我妈妈
My mom.
如果我...
If I had just...
听进去艾莉西娅的话
taken Alicia seriously.
得了  别那么想
Come on, man, you can't think like that.
别说了
Just stop talking.
求你
Please.
好啊
Sure.
我们去买点东西
We'll, uh, go get some supplies.
我们得...
We have to, uh --
我们得火葬他们  麦克斯
We gotta burn the bodies, Max.
就像我爸爸
Like my dad.
我来吧
I can do it.
我...
I...
该由我来
I should do it.
你俩走吧
You two get out of here.
-麦克斯  我们...  -拜托了
- Max, we would - Please.
拜托
Please just...
你做得对
You did the right thing.
你救了他
You saved him.
嗯
Yeah.
是啊  他看上去很好呢
Yeah, he seemed super saved.
我看着他们
You know, I was watching them this
有爱的一家人
loving family.
就像我们本该的那样
The kind we should've had.
现在  突然就没了
And now just like that, it's gone.
迪恩  你不能让麦克斯
Dean, you couldn't let Max
出卖灵魂的
make some deal for his soul.
萨姆  我们经常为了救彼此
Sam, we do terrible things all the time
做很过分的事
to save each other.
为了家人这是应该的
I mean, that's what you do for family.
我凭什么阻止他
Who am I to stop him?
他很坚强  他不会有事的
Well, he's strong. He'll be all right.
嗯  我不太确定
Yeah, I'm not so sure.
怎么回事  我觉得...
What happened? I feel...
我觉得好像喝多了龙舌兰
Ugh, I feel like I drank too much tequila.
你做了什么  怎么...
What...w-what did you do? What...
-你受伤了吗  -没有
- Are you hurt? - No, no, no, no. I-I...
我回头再解释
I'll explain everything.
但我们得走了  好吗
But we gotta go now. Okay?
好
Okay.
(妈妈)
是我  抱歉我之前没接
Hey, it's me. Sorry I couldn't pick up before.
我跟凯奇猎魔去了
I've been on a hunt with Ketch.
很抱歉我一直没有陪伴你和萨姆
I'm sorry I haven't been there for you and Sam,
但我想陪你们
but I wanna be.
我会的
I will be.
我只是  需要完成这个
I just...I need to finish this.
我想你们
I miss you boys.
我爱你们
I love you.
(妈妈)
迪恩  打给我
Dean, call me.
我们有麻烦了
We've got a problem.
萨姆  是妈妈  出事了
Sam? Hey, it's Mom. Something's wrong.
萨姆
Sam!
很高兴你醒来了
Good of you to rejoin me.
电击枪
A Taser?
不太公平啊
Not really a fair fight.
如果你能像我希望的那么无情
If only you'd been as ruthless as I hoped,
结果就会很好的
this could have worked out.
记住  玛丽
Remember, Mary,
我给过你机会
I gave you a chance.
现在怎么办
So now what?
你要杀了我吗
You kill me?
(迪恩)
别傻了
Don't be silly.
你是个资源
You're an asset.
我们对你另有安排
We have other plans for you.
好了  玛丽
Now, Mary...
我们开始吧
Let's begin.